weather.us 2018-12-27

# Privacy Notice | Weather.us

Last updated on January 15th, 2018 

This Privacy Notice describes how WeatherOK Inc. ("WeatherOK" or "we") collects, uses, or shares data obtained from you when you use its services at weather.us and weathermodels.com (the "Sites").

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY NOTICE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE SITES. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITES NOW, OR FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE, WILL INDICATE ACCEPTANCE BY YOU OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY NOTICE, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITES.

**1 Collection of Personal Data, User Data and Location Data**

1.1 Summary. WeatherOK collects information about its users at Account registration, when contacted by users or customers, and through technologies that provide information about you when you browse our Sites, as described herein.

1.2 Personal Data. As part of the Account registration process, we ask for your name, email address, password, display name, company, billing address, and payment card information ("Personal Data"). You are required to provide this Personal Data when you register. WeatherOK treats Personal Data confidentially and does not sell or rent your Personal Data to third parties.

1.3 User Data. When you use the Sites, we receive information generated through the use of the Sites ("User Data"). For example, we may collect usage and log data about how you access or use the Sites. We may also collect your IP address, operating system information, language settings, unique device identifiers, or other diagnostic or analytics data.

1.4 Location Data. In order to provide weather services that are relevant to your location, we may collect your location information ("Location Data"). We may collect information about the searches you run on the Sites, including requests for weather data in specific geographic locations. We may also collect information about your location based on your IP address or based on precise location data shared by your mobile phone or web browser (based on GPS, IP address, cell site information, or other real-time geographic location technologies).

**2 Use or Sharing of Personal Data, User Data, and Location Data**

2.1 Summary. WeatherOK may use or share your Personal Data, User Data, and/or Location Data to support the provision of services on our Sites, as described herein.

2.2 We use Personal Data, User Data, and Location Data to provide and maintain services; to address service, security, or customer support issues; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, unlawful, or technical issues; as required by law; to fulfill our contracts; to improve or enhance our services; or to provide analysis or valuable information to our customers and users.

2.3 We use Personal Data to authenticate your access to your account; for purposes of billing customers or collecting debts; to respond to you if you contact us; or to send you messages about our products and services.

2.4 WeatherOK shares Personal Data with its third party financial transaction vendor with whom WeatherOK has a contractual relationship in order to process payments and subscriptions, and to create accurate invoices.

WEATHEROK HAS NO CONTROL OVER THE PRIVACY, SECURITY, OR DATA COLLECTION PRACTICES OF ITS THIRD PARTY VENDORS. WEATHEROK HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND LIABILITY FOR, AND MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO, THE PRIVACY, SECURITY, AND DATA COLLECTION PRACTICES OF ITS THIRD PARTY VENDORS, INCLUDING ITS THIRD PARTY FINANCIAL TRANSACTION VENDOR.

2.5 Google Analytics. Some or all of the Sites make use of Google Analytics, which provides analytics about customers and users of the Sites, allowing WeatherOK to recognize and understand user preferences, make improvements to the Sites, choose content and advertising to display, and accomplish other business purposes. Google may use its own tracking technologies to collect information about your use of the Sites. Click here to opt-out of Google Analytics or use the Google Analytics Opt- Out Browser Add On at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

2.6 Advertising. Some of the Sites may display advertising, including behavioral advertising. We use third party advertising vendors that may collect information about your use of the Sites and use the collected information to display advertising to you. This means your internet viewing behaviors or practices, even on other websites not controlled by WeatherOK, may be used for the purpose of choosing advertising to display to you. Third party advertising networks provide tools to opt-out of such advertising on all websites, including here: <https://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

2.7 Do Not Track. WeatherOK does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. WeatherOK does not itself use tracking technologies to track users when they cross to third party websites, but its advertising vendors and analytics vendors may do so, to the extent described in Sections 2.6 and 2.7.

2.8 Cookies. Our third party advertising, analytics, and financial transaction vendors may place cookies on your device. WeatherOK may also place cookies on your device for purposes of account authentication and as an identity token. You may be required to accept cookies in order for the Sites to function appropriately. To learn more about cookies and how to delete them, follow this link: <https://www.aboutcookies.org/>.

**3 Compliance Statements**

3.1 Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. The Sites are not intended for use by children under the age of 13\. Children under the age of 13 are prohibited from registering to use the Sites. If you are under the age of 13, do not register to use the Sites.

3.2 Law Enforcement Requests. Law enforcement requests for data may be directed to [joerg@weather.us](mailto:joerg@weather.us). We comply with lawful law enforcement requests.

**4 Your Privacy Rights**

4.1 You may close your account using the My Account portal at any time. When you close your account, WeatherOK will delete data associated with your account, including Personal Data, User Data, and/or Location Data. This data will not be recoverable.

4.2 You may change your responses to registration questions using the My Account portal.

4.3 If you have any additional questions or requests regarding the privacy of your data, please contact WeatherOK at [contact@weather.us](mailto:contact@weather.us).

**5 Changes to this Privacy Notice**

5.1 This Privacy Notice may be changed at any time without notice to you. You will be notified by email of any Material Changes to this Privacy Notice.

5.2 Material Changes include only changes to the categories of third parties with whom WeatherOK shares Personal Data it collects when you register for an Account.

5.3 If you disagree with any changes to this Privacy Notice, you may delete your account before the effective date of the change.

**6 Contact Information**

If you have questions about this Privacy Notice, please contact:
